<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Valorant Agent</string>
    <string name="agent_name">Agent Names</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_name">Rama Adji Prasetyo</string>
    <string name="about_email">ramaadjiprsty@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="abilites_title">Ability</string>

    <string-array name="data_agent">
        <item>KAY/O</item>
        <item>Sova</item>
        <item>Chamber</item>
        <item>Sage</item>
        <item>Jett</item>
        <item>Omen</item>
        <item>Brimstone</item>
        <item>Skye</item>
        <item>Neon</item>
        <item>Astra</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="agent_description">
        <item>KAY/O is a machine of war built for a single purpose: neutralizing radiants. His power to Suppress enemy abilities dismantles his opponents capacity to fight back, securing him and his allies the ultimate edge.</item>
        <item>Born from the eternal winter of Russia tundra, Sova tracks, finds, and eliminates enemies with ruthless efficiency and precision. His custom bow and incredible scouting abilities ensure that even if you run, you cannot hide.</item>
        <item>Well-dressed and well-armed, French weapons designer Chamber expels aggressors with deadly precision. He leverages his custom arsenal to hold the line and pick off enemies from afar, with a contingency built for every plan.</item>
        <item>The stronghold of China, Sage creates safety for herself and her team wherever she goes. Able to revive fallen friends and stave off aggressive pushes, she provides a calm center to a hellish fight.</item>
        <item>Representing her home country of South Korea, Jett agile and evasive fighting style lets her take risks no one else can. She runs circles around every skirmish, cutting enemies before they even know what hit them.</item>
        <item>A phantom of a memory, Omen hunts in the shadows. He renders enemies blind, teleports across the field, then lets paranoia take hold as his foe scrambles to learn where he might strike next.</item>
        <item>Joining from the U.S.A., Brimstone orbital arsenal ensures his squad always has the advantage. His ability to deliver utility precisely and safely make him the unmatched boots-on-the-ground commander.</item>
        <item>Hailing from Australia, Skye and her band of beasts trail-blaze the way through hostile territory. With her creations hampering the enemy, and her power to heal others, the team is strongest and safest by Skye’s side.</item>
        <item>Filipino Agent Neon surges forward at shocking speeds, discharging bursts of bioelectric radiance as fast as her body generates it. She races ahead to catch enemies off guard, then strikes them down quicker than lightning.</item>
        <item>Ghanaian Agent Astra harnesses the energies of the cosmos to reshape battlefields to her whim. With full command of her astral form and a talent for deep strategic foresight, shes always eons ahead of her enemy next move.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="agent_icon">
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/f/f0/KAYO_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230523180711</item> <!--kayo-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/4/49/Sova_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230523180933</item> <!--sova-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/0/09/Chamber_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230523180616</item> <!--chamber-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/7/74/Sage_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230606161159</item> <!--sage-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/3/35/Jett_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230909031447</item> <!--jett-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/b/b0/Omen_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230523180801</item> <!--omen-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/4/4d/Brimstone_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230523180558</item> <!--brimstone-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/3/33/Skye_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230606161546</item> <!--skye-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/d/d0/Neon_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230523180744</item> <!--neon-->
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/valorant/images/0/08/Astra_icon.png/revision/latest?cb=20230523180525</item> <!--astra-->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="agent_abilites">
        <item>ZERO/point – KAY/O equips a suppression blade that, when thrown, sticks to the first surface it hits. The knife then winds up and suppresses anyone caught in the explosion radius, rendering their abilities useless.\n\n
            FLASH/drive – KAY/O equips a flash grenade that explodes after its thrown, blinding enemies in its line of sight. Right-clicking the grenade causes it to only cook for one second before exploding. Left-clicking cooks the flash for 1.6 seconds longer.\n\n
            FRAG/ment – KAY/O equips an explosive fragment that sticks to the floor when thrown. The fragment explodes multiple times and deals near lethal damage at the center with each explosion. Each of the three pulses deals between 25 and 60 points of damage, depending on how close the enemy is to the center.\n\n
            Ultimate: NULL/cmd – KAY/O instantly overloads with polarized radianite energy, empowering him and causing large energy pulses to emit from his location. Enemies hit with the pulses are suppressed for a short duration. KAY/O also gains a combat stim while overloaded. If the robot is killed while overloaded, he’s downed and enters a destabilized state that allows allies to revive him by stabilizing his core.</item>
        <item>Shock Bolt - Fires an explosive bolt that emits a damaging pulse of static energy upon impact.\n\n
            Owl Drone - Deploys a controllable drone that can fire a dart to reveal enemies in its line of sight.\n\n
            Recon Bolt - Fires a bolt that deploys a sonar emitter, revealing the location of enemies in its area.\n\n
            Hunters Fury (Ultimate) - Fires up to three deadly energy blasts that spear across the entire map, revealing and damaging enemies caught in their path.</item>
        <item>Trademark – Place a trap that scans for enemies. When a visible enemy comes in range, the trap counts down and then destabilizes the terrain around them, creating a lingering field that slows players caught inside of it.\n\n
            Headhunter – Activate to equip a heavy pistol. Alt fire with the pistol equipped to aim down sights. Holds eight bullets at max.\n\n
            Rendezvous – Place a single teleport anchor. While on the ground and in range of the anchor, reactivate to quickly teleport to the anchor. Anchor can be picked up and redeployed, but not if it is destroyed.\n\n
            Ultimate – Tour de Force – Activate to summon a powerful, custom sniper rifle that will kill an enemy with any direct hit to the upper body. Killing an enemy creates a lingering field that slows players caught inside of it.</item>
        <item>Slow Orb – Cast out a radianite orb that breaks into a slowing field upon impact with the ground. All caught in the field are slowed, grounded, and make noise when moving.\n\n
            Barrier Orb – Conjure a large, solid wall. Right-click to rotate the wall before casting.\\n
            Healing Orb – Heal an ally or yourself to full health over a few seconds.\n\n
            Ultimate: Resurrection – Target a friendly corpse. After a short delay, revive them with full health.</item>
        <item>Cloudburst – Throw out a cloud of fog that obscures vision on impact. Hold down the ability button to bend the cloud’s in-flight trajectory.\n\n
            Updraft – After a brief wind-up, propel yourself upward.\n\n
            Tailwind – Prepare a gust of wind for a limited time. Activate to propel yourself in the direction you are moving. Resets after two kills.\n\n
            Ultimate: Blade Storm – Arm yourself with several deadly throwing knives that deal moderate damage and kill on headshots. Scoring a kill restores all daggers. Left-click throws a single dagger. Right-click throws all remaining daggers in a short-ranged burst, but right-click kills do not restore daggers.</item>
        <item>Paranoia – Send out an Ethereal shadow in a straight line, Nearsighting anyone it touches\n\n
            Shadow Walk – After a delay, dematerialize and teleport a short distance.\n\n
            Dark Cover – Cast out a stealthed ethereal orb that bursts into an obscuring sphere of shadow at its final location. Can be charged to increase distance.\n\n
            Ultimate: From the Shadows – Select anywhere on the map to teleport and reform. When arriving, appear as a Shade, that will go back to your original location if killed. Once the teleport is complete, become Incorporeal for a short time.</item>
        <item>Incendiary – Launch an incendiary grenade that deploys a damaging field of fire. Fire lasts for seven seconds and deals 60 points of damage per second.\n\n
            Stim Beacon – Drop a Stim Beacon on the ground, granting a Combat Stim and speed boost to players nearby. Players get improved weapon equip speed, fire rate, reload speed, recovery speed, and movement speed.\n\n
            Sky Smoke – Use your map to call in up to three orbital deployment smokescreens that obscure vision. Click to set the locations, and confirm to launch. Each smoke lasts 19.25 seconds.\n\n
            Ultimate: Orbital Strike – Use your map to target a location, launching a devastating orbital strike that pulses for high damage over several seconds. Deals 20 damage per tick, with 6.67 ticks per second across a three second duration.</item>
        <item>Trailblazer – Skye equips a Tasmanian tiger trinket. Fire to send out and take control of the predator. Players can fire again to leap forward as the tiger, exploding in a concussive blast and damaging enemies directly hit by it.\n\n
            Guiding Light – Skye equips a hawk trinket. Fire to send it forward and hold fire to guide the hawk in the direction of your crosshair, similar to Jett’s smokes or Phoenix’s wall. Players can reuse the ability while the hawk is in the air to flash anyone caught in the blind. If an enemy is caught by the flash, the hawk will play a hit-confirm sound.\n\n
            Regrowth – Skye equips a healing trinket. Hold fire to channel, healing allies in range and in Skye’s line of sight. The ability can be reused until her healing pool is depleted. Skye can’t heal herself.\n\n
            Ultimate: Seekers – Skye equips a Seeker trinket. Fire to send out three Seekers that track down the three closest enemies, nearsighting those caught.</item>
        <item>High Gear – Instantly channel Neon’s power for increased speed. When charged, use Alt Fire to trigger an electric slide. Slide charge resets after two kils.\n\n
            Relay Bolt – Instantly throw an energy bolt that bounces once. Upon hitting each surface, the bolt electrifies the ground below with a concussive blast.\n\n
            Fast Lane – Fire two energy lines forward on the ground that extend a short distance or until they hit a surface. The lines rise into walls of static electricity that block vision and damage enemies passing through them.\n\n
            Ultimate: Overdrive – Unleash Neon’s full power and speed for a short duration. Fire to channel the power into deadly a lightning beam with high movement accuracy. The duration resets on each kill.</item>
        <item>Gravity Well – Activate a Star to form a Gravity Well. Players in the area are pulled toward the center before it explodes, making all players still trapped inside fragile Vulnerable for 2.75 secvonds.\n\n
            Nova Pulse – Activate a Star to detonate a Nova Pulse. The Nova Pulse charges briefly then strikes, concussing all players in its area for 1.25 seconds\n\n
            Nebula – Activate a Star to transform it into a Nebula (smoke) that lasts for 14.24 seconds.\n\n
            Dissipate – Use (F) on a Star to Dissipate it, returning the star to be placed in a new location after a delay. Dissipate briefly forms a fake Nebula at the Star’s location before returning.\n\n
            Ultimate: Astral Form / Cosmic Divide – Activate to enter Astral Form where you can place Stars with primary fire. Stars can be reactivated later, transforming them into a Nova Pulse, Nebula, or Gravity Well. When Cosmic Divide is charged, use secondary fire in Astral Form to begin aiming it, then primary fire to select two locations. An infinite Cosmic Divide connects the two points you select. Cosmic Divide blocks bullets and heavily dampens audio.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>